(Sheldon:)Good evening.
(Sheldon:)I'm your guest lecturer,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)I was expecting applause,
(Sheldon:)but I suppose stunned silence
is equally appropriate.
(Sheldon:)I agreed to speak
to you this evening,
(Sheldon:)because I was told that you're
the best and the brightest
(Sheldon:)of this university's
doctoral candidates.
(Sheldon:)Hmm. Of course,
that's like saying
(Sheldon:)you are the most important
electron in a hydrogen atom.
'Cause, you see,
(Sheldon:)there's only one electron
in a hydrogen atom.
(Sheldon:)Best and brightest,
my sweet patootie.
(Sheldon:)All right, let's begin.
(Sheldon:)Show of hands,
who here is familiar
(Sheldon:)with the concept
of topological insulators?
(Sheldon:)Don't kid yourselves.
(Leonard:)I found another tweet from a
student at Sheldon's lecture.